{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"289","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d57\u0d15","option2":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d47\u0d39\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2e \u00a0","option3":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02","option4":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"613","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d0f\u0d15\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d07\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d38\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d02\u0d32","option3":"\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d38\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"173","question":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d47\u0d17\u0d02 ?","option1":"2.12 km\/sec","option2":"2.11 km\/sec","option3":"2.38 km\/sec","option4":"2.36 km\/sec","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"334","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d39\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30","option4":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"528","question":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ?","option1":"606 \u2013 647","option2":"610 \u2013 650","option3":"600 \u2013 648","option4":"580 \u2013 640","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"7","question":"\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d","option2":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option3":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"432","question":"\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d :","option1":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f","option2":"\u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f","option3":"\u0d39\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d28\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"272","question":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 ","option2":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"469","question":"\"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02 :","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d33\u0d42\u0d30\u0d41","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d38\u0d42\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"83","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d\u200c","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d. \u0d2c\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u200c","answer":"1"}]},"code":"100"}
